Wadsworth Family Papers 1790-1950
Wadsworth Family Papers
- Persons Who Worked for the Wadsworths as Farm or Day Laborers, 1831-1842; 5 ledgers
  - Farm Accounts and Hired Hands, April, 12 1841-June 9, 1841:; D (Box unwrapped)
Sumner and Hopkins, Merchants in Boston, MA, Bill 1839. Wadsworth, William Wolcott Dishes and tableware, Example of vouchers' scope. Box V1 Household Sh 27
Sumner, Charles (1811-1874) Senator and Orator, Letters from (6) 1848-1859. Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Friends in Boston. Box LEAW2 Fs16,17 Sh 24
Sumner, Charles (1811-1874) Senator and Orator, Letters from (9) 1870. Wadsworth,William Austin Trip around the world; letters of introduction. Box LWAW3 F 73 Shelf 26
Swan, Charles F Commission Merchant, Letters from (2) 1884; 1905. Wadsworth,William Austin Hunt; Congress Hotel in Avon; plans for renovation. Box LWAW3 F 75 Shelf 26
Swift, Isabella, Friend "Belle", Letters to (5) 1842-1850. Wadsworth,Elizabeth Wads. Murray Personal and family news. Box LWAW4 F 13 Shelf 26
Swift, Isabella, Geneva NY Friend "Belle", Letter from 4/13/1839. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Personal. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Swift, Philetus, Settler and Assemblyman Ontario Co, Letter to February 19, 1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Henrietta: opposition to dividing the township in two. Bk 61 P 331 Shelf 27
Symington, (William) Stuart ( 1901-) NY Senator, Letter from 1934. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Platform for Republican Party. Box J112D F 14 Sh 59
Tax Assessors, Letters to (16) 1815-1819. Wadsworth, James (1768-1844) Taxes on unsold lots in various townships. Bk 61 Sh 27 use index
Temple Hill Cemetery, Deeds for lots, 1800 's. Wadsworth family Temple Hill Cemetery lot owners on pages 93-95, 294 in Deeds JS and WW Shelf 46
Temple Hill House Plans Wadsworth,William Wolcott Temple Hill house plans and directions. File Cab. 1 Drawer 2
Terry, Adrian Russell, Letters from (9) 1826-1834. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Personal. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Terry, Charles Appleton (1858-1839) Attorney, Letters from (4) 1831-1832. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Personal. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Terry, Nathaniel (1768-1844) Congressman, Letter to March 20, 1819. Wadsworth,James (1768-i844) Farming as a vocation; Advice for Terry's son. Bk 61 P 508 Shelf 27
Terry, Nathaniel (1768-1844) Congressman, Letters to (21) 1805-1819. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Personal and Public Affairs; Index in print and on film Lib Congress Microfilm
Thayer, Edwin Pope (b.1864) Secretary, US Senate 1925-1933, Letters to (2) June 1927. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Aviation Club for boys. Box J112E F 1
Thompson, George, Connecticut attorney, Letter to March 20, 1839. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Connecticut estates; Sale of lands in Huntingdon. Box LBk 1 P 43 Sh 27
Tibbits, Elisha, New York Insurance company president Letter to November 26, 1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Mill on Conesus outlet for milling flour described. Bk 61 P 457 Shelf 27
Tibbits, Elisha, New York Insurance company president Letter to October 7, 1816. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Weather, 1816 "year of 1800 and froze to death"; crops. Bk 61 P 159 Shelf 27
Tibbits, Elisha, New York Insurance company president Letters to (36) 1815-1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Wool; cattle and other farm business; power of attorney. Bk 61 Sh 27 use index
Tibbits, George (1763-1849) State Senator, Letters to (13) 1815-1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Politics in New York State and other social issues. Bk 61 Sh 27 use index
Tibbits, George (1763-1849) State Senator, Letter to March 18, 1816. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Religion and Newspapers, State support for. Bk 61 P 78 Shelf 27
Tiffany Glass Company, Letters to (1 folder) 1889. Wadsworth,William Austin Stained glass window for Episcopal Church. File Cab. I, Drawer 2
Tilden, Samuel Jones (1814-1886) Governor of NY 1874, Letter from 8/6/1852. Wadsworth,James S. (1867-1864) Politics. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Tonawanda Reservation, Deeds (2 files) 1823-1874. Wadsworth,James and James S. Indian land sales. File Cab. 1 Drawer 2
Tonawanda Reservation, Map 19th century Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Indian lands. See Also Indian Treaty of 1838. Map File #1 Main Set
Townsend, I and J Troy Iron and Nails Store, Albany Letter to and order June 2, 1817. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Fireplace fire box for the Homestead. Bk 61 P 237 Shelf 27
Townsend, Jacob, Lewiston NY, Letter to January 17, 1816. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) War of 1812; land site of fort at Lewiston Heights. Bk 61 P 39 Shelf 27
Tremont House, Boston, MA, Bills (4) 1839, 1841. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Hotel lodging and food: Example of vouchers' scope. Box V1 Hotels Shelf 27
Troup, Robert, Lawyer and Pulteney Estate agent, Letters to (23) August 26, 1815+. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Pulteney contracts: Disputed policies and commissions. Bk 61 sh 27 use index
True, Moses, James' land agent in Oakfield Letter to March 10, 1842. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Erie Canal feeder lands for sale Oak Orchard Creek area. Box LBk 1 P 73 Sh 27
Trumbull, John (1756-1843) Painter and patriot, Letter from (Copy) 1818. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Battle of Bunker Hill. Box J112D F 15 sh 59
Trumbull, John (1756-1843) Painter and patriot, Letter to October 2, 1815. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Morris Tract; Mt. Morris. Bk 61 P 14 Shelf 27
Trumbull, John (1756-1843) Painter and patriot, Letter to April 19, 1819. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Wentworth, Thomas Painter of Niagara Falls scenes. Bk 61 P 520 Shelf 27
Tucker, B Blacksmith, Bills (3) 1837-1839. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Blacksmith services. Examples of vouchers' scope, Box V1 Blacksmith Sh 27
Tucker, Luther (1802-1873) Editor Genesee Farmer Letters from (2) 1842. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Farming. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Tucker, Luther (1802-1873) Editor Genesee Farmer Letter to December 16, 1842. Wadsworth,William Wolcott
Agent-(Book 58)
Genesee Farmer price; Subscriptions for tenant farmers. Box LBkl P Shelf 27
Turner, George F Army officer, Letters from (11) 1828-1841. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Personal. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Turner, Powers and Company, Letter to March 4, 1839. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Genesee Valley Canal to use stone from Street Farm. Box LBk 1 P 43 Sh 27
Twachtman, John H (1853-1902) Artist, Letter from September 22, 1895. Wadsworth,William Austin Yellowstone Park; Inspiration from same. Box LWAW4 F 7 Shelf 26
Ullman, Sol, Assistant Attorney General of NY, Letters to and from (2) 1934. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Politics; Congressman Wm. Sirovich. Box J112D F 16 Sh 59
Van Buren, John (1810-1866) Son of and aide to Pres. Martin, Letters from (17) 1834-1848. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Personal and Politics. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Van Buren, John (1810-1866) Son of and aide to Pres. Martin, Letter to November 28, 1839. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Slave: He would buy the freedom of a runaway. Box LBk 1 P 41 Sh 27
Van Buren, Martin (1782-1862) President of the US, Letter to May 2, 1839. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Indian Treaty of 1838: Judge Stryker's wish to be Agent. Box L8k 1 P 51 Sh 27
Van Buren, Martin (1782-1862) President of the US, Letter to June 30, 1840. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Indian Treaty of 1838: Removal of Agent; Chiefs complain Box LBk 1 P 56 Sh 27
Van Buren, Martin (1782-1862) 8th US President Letters Patent (22) 1837-1839. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Michigan lands. Box 94A Shelf 53
Van Buren, Martin (1782-1862) 8th US President Letters Patent, (3) 1839 Wadsworth,William Wolcott Michigan lands. Box CM2 Shelf 14
Van Buren, Martin (1782-1862) 8th US President Letters Patent (3) 1837. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Ohio lands. Box 94A Shelf 53
Van Buren, Martin (1782-1862) President of the US, Letters from (9) 1838-1851. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Personal and Politics. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Van Buren, Martin (1782-1862) President of the US, Letter to December 10, 1839. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Postmaster appointment of George A. Tiffany of Geneseo. Box LBk 1 P 39 Sh 27
Van Fossen, John, New York State legislator, Letter to March 2, 1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Bridge at Avon; Tolls; Turnpike from Moscow to Dunkirk. Bk 61 P 344 Shelf 27
Van Gorder, Greenleaf S (1855-) Buffalo Attorney, Letters from (8) 1898-1900. Wadsworth,William Austin Politics. Box LWAW4 F 9 Shelf 26
Van Ness, William W, Hudson NY State Sup. Court Judge, Letter to February 26, 1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Counties: Objection to subdivision of Genesee and Ontario. Bk 61 P 340 Shelf 27
Van Rensselaer, Cornelia, Stephen's 2nd wife; see Patterson Letters from (2) 1830-1831. Wadsworth,Daniel (1771~1848) Personal. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Van Rensselaer, Solomon (1774-1852) Officer, War of 1812, Letter to January 30, 1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Counties: Objection to subdivision of Geneseo and Ontario. Bk 61 P 378 Shelf 27
Van Rensselaer, Solomon, (1774-1852) Officer, War of 1812, Letter to March 29, 1819. Wadsworth,William (1761-1833) Militia morale and appearance; Inspections to come. 8k 61 P 513 Shelf 27
Van Rensselaer, Stephen (1764-1839) Federalist "Patroon," Letter from 3/16/1825. Wadsworth,Daniel (1771-1848) Personal. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Wadsworth Family, Geneseo, NY, Account Books (7) 1790-1817, 1839. Wadsworth,William and James Farm and personal expenses; Misc. early books. Box AJ 1-3 Shelf 2
Wadsworth Family, Geneseo, NY, Secondary sources. Wadsworth,James to William P Obituaries and other printed material filed by name. File Cab. I, Drawer 1
Wadsworth Farms, Geneseo, NY, Farm and Workers Accounts (4 books) 1834-1842. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844)
Agent Winans, Theo. and others,
Farm work assignments; Expenses; Workers' accounts. Box WA1 Shelf 3
Wadsworth Farms, Geneseo, NY, Farm and Workers Accounts 1827; 1831-1842. (1 book). Wadsworth,James (1768-1844)
Agent-Winans, Theo. and others,
Farm work assignments; Expenses; Workers' accounts. Shelf 3 use index
Wadsworth Library, Geneseo, NY, Records 1901+. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Library financial reports, etc. Box J 107 Shelf 57
Wadsworth, A S, Letters (29 folders) 1870+. Wadsworth family Ohio Ditch Law, etc. File Cab. I, Drawer 2
Wadsworth, Cornelia (1812-1831) Sister, Letters from (16) 1825-1831. Wadsworth, James S. and William W. Family and personal. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Wadsworth. Craig W., Jr., Geneseo cousin; Diplomat, Letters from (4) 1904. Wadsworth, William Austin Family business. Box LWAW4 F 12 Shelf 26
Wadsworth. Craig W., Sr. (1841-1872) son of General James S Letter from June 7. 1870. Wadsworth, William Austin Family business. Box LWAW4 F 11 Shelf 26
Wadsworth, Daniel (1771-1848) Hartford CT. Letters to (150) 1820-1837. Wadsworth, James and Others Family and Business. Index in print and on film Lib Congress Microfilm
Wadsworth. Daniel (1771-1848) Hartford CT. Letter to August 22. 1814. Wadsworth, James (1768-1844) Homestead plans for new addition, thank you. Lib Congress Microfilm
Wadsworth, Decius (1768-1821) Connecticut Colonel. Letters to (7) November 25. 1815+. Wadsworth, James (1768-1844) Family and Business. Bk 61 Sh 27 use index
Wadsworth. Elizabeth (1815-1851) Sister, Letters from (47) 1830-1845. Wadsworth, William Wolcott Geneseo and family news; See also Elizabeth Murray. Box Ll-L4 See Calendars
Wadsworth, Elizabeth. (1815-1851) Sister, Letter from January 29. 1839 Wadsworth, William Wolcott Cattle: Care in bad winter weather. Box L2 Shelf 15
Wadsworth, Emmeline (1808-1885) Wife of Wm. Wolcott, Letter to March 8, 1866. Wadsworth, Emmeline Austin
Agent-Allen, Hezekiah,
Geneseo; support of old and indigent retainers. Box LMiscl Shelf 24
Wadsworth. Emmeline (1808-1885) Wife of Wm. Wolcott, Documents (15 folders) 1853-1854. Wadsworth, Emmeline Austin Guardianship of infant children after father's death. File Cab. I, Drawer 2
Wadsworth, Emmeline Austin (1808-1885) Wife of Wm. Wolcott, Letter to August 3, 1865. Wadsworth, Emmeline Austin
Agent-Allen, Hezekiah.
Homestead: condition and upkeep while she was absent. Box LMiscl Shelf 24
Wadsworth, Emmeline Austin (1808-1885) Wife of Wm. Wolcott, Letters from (35) 1862-1882. Wadsworth, William Austin Personal and family news; Business. Box LWAW4 Fs 14-18 Sh26
Wadsworth, Evelyn Peters (1845-1886) Wife of Craig W. Jr., Letter from June 26, 18?? Wadsworth, William Austin Wadsworth, Craig W. Jr. General James S. Box LWAW6 F 24 Shelf 26
Wadsworth, Faith Trumbull (1769-1846) Wife of Daniel, Letters to and from (15) 1826-1832. Wadsworth, Daniel (1771-1848) Family and personal. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Wadsworth, Herbert (1851-1927) Avon Inventor/Poet, Diaries (2 volumes) 1883 and 1884. Wadsworth, Herbert (1851-1927) Ashantee Estate. Box WHl Shelf 37
Wadsworth, Herbert (1851-1927) Avon Inventor/Poet, Letters from (7 folds) 1871-1905. Wadsworth, William Austin Family and Business. Box LWAW4 Shelf 26
Wadsworth, Herbert (1851-1927) Avon Inventor/Poet, Letters from (11) 1899-1900. Wadsworth, William Austin Family and Business. Box LWAW4 Sh 26
Wadsworth, Herbert (1851-1927) Avon Inventor/Poet, Letters from (24) 1877-1883. Wadsworth, Emmeline Austin Family and friends. Box LEAW2 F 21 Shelf 24
Wadsworth, Herbert (1851-1927) Avon Inventor/Poet, Breeding Records (2 vs) 1890-1933. Wadsworth, Herbert (1851-1927) Horses at Ashantee. Box WHl Shelf 37
Wadsworth, Herbert (1851-1927) Avon Inventor/Poet, Poems (2 sets) Wadsworth, Herbert (1851-1927) Poetry about the Genesee Valley and his experiences. Boxes WH2 and WH3 Sh 37
Wadsworth, James (1768-1844) Geneseo Settler, Newspaper collection, 1795-1850. Wadsworth, James (1768-1844) Advertising and news from New York State and eastern US. 4 Bound volumes Sh 40
Wadsworth, James (1819-) Buffalo, Correspondence, etc., 1850+. Wadsworth, James (1819-) Buffalo lands, etc. See Index Wads 3029.5 W125 A5. New York State Library
Wadsworth, James (1768-1844) Geneseo settler, 1818-1838. Wadsworth, James (1768-1844) Education in New York State; Cited by Legislature 1843. File Cab. I, Drawer 2
Wadsworth, James (1768-1844) Geneseo settler, Letters from (130) 1793-1843. Wadsworth, Jeremiah, Daniel, Sons Family and Business. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Wadsworth, James (1768-1844) Geneseo settler, Letter from February 22, 1799. Wadsworth, Jeremiah (1743-1804) Handwriting. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Wadsworth, James (1768-1844) Geneseo settler, Letters from (2) and list 1843. Wadsworth, James S and William W Libraries at Homestead and for the people of Geneseo. File Cab. I, Drawer 2
Wadsworth, James (1768-1844) Geneseo settler, Documents (4 folders) 18??-1905. Wadsworth family Libraries in Geneseo; Reading Room. File Cab. I, Drawer 2
Wadsworth, James (1768-1844) Geneseo settler, Letter from February 6, 1801. Wadsworth, Jeremiah (1743-1804) Marriage prospects and ideas about marriage. Lib Congress Microfilm
Wadsworth, James (1768-1844) Geneseo settler, Letter from November 19, 1841. Wadsworth, James S and William W Wadsworth Estate; Division of responsibilities. Lib Congress Microfilm
Wadsworth. James (1768-1844) Geneseo settler, Correspondence, etc., 1792-1844. Wadsworth, James (1768-s844) Wadsworth lands, etc. See Index Wads 3029.5 W125 A5. New York State Library
Wadsworth, James C Connecticut relative, Letter from January 10, 1846. Wadsworth, William Wolcott Manual Labor School; Wished to teach young farmers. Bx L4 Shelf 15
Wadsworth, James Samuel (1807-1864) General in Civil War, Will (1 folder) 1864. Wadsworth, James S (1807-1864) Bequests. File Cab. I, Drawer 2
Wadsworth, James Samuel (1807-1864) General in Civil War, Letter from May 3, 1864. Wadsworth, Mary Craig Wharton Civil War; his last letter to her and his sons. Lib Congress Microfilm
Wadsworth, James Samuel (1807-1864) General in Civil War, Collected family papers 1793-1862. Wadsworth, James Samuel and Family Family and Business. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Wadsworth, James Samuel (1807-1864) General in Civil War, Letters from (50+) 1832+. Wadsworth, William Wolcott Family and Business. Use calendars in Box L1+ Shelf 15
Wadsworth, James Samuel (1807-1864) General in Civil War, Job descriptions, [1836]-1854. Wadsworth, James Samuel Office Clerk; Outdoor Clerk; Overseer of Estate in 1854 Box D Shelf 46 p 5-13
Wadsworth, James Samuel (1807-1864) General in Civil War. Inventory of records 1790-1836. Wadsworth, James Samuel Wadsworth Family records stored in 8 boxes, 1836. Box D Shelf 46 P 63
Wadsworth, James Wolcott Jr (1877-1952) Geneseo; NY Senator, Memorandum 3/25/1932. Wadsworth, James Wolcott, Jr. Constitutional Amendments; Wayne Johnson Brief Box J112E F 6 Shelf 59
Wadsworth, James Wolcott Jr (1877-1952) Geneseo; NY Senator, Letters to and from (15) 1923-1928. Wadsworth, James Wolcott, Jr. Educational topics. Box J112E F 7 Sh 59
Wadsworth, James Wolcott Jr (1877-1952) Geneseo; NY Senator, Letters to and Documents 1926-1927. Wadsworth, James Wolcott, Jr. Farming; Cattle; Speech to Saddle and Sirloin Club. Box J112E F 9 Sh 59
Wadsworth, James Wolcott Jr (1877-1952) Geneseo; NY Senator, Documents (3) 1927. Wadsworth, James Wolcott, Jr. Federal Reserve System. Box J112E F 10 Sh 59
Wadsworth, James Wolcott Jr (1877-1952) Geneseo; NY Senator, Speech Wadsworth, James Wolcott, Jr. National Defense; Lincoln's army. Box J112E F 22 Sh 59
Wadsworth, James Wolcott Jr (1877-1952) Geneseo; NY Senator, Letters to and Documents (11 boxes) 1914-1932. Wadsworth, James Wolcott, Jr. Political subjects; Business and Personal letters. Boxes J112A-K Shs 59-60
Wadsworth, James Wolcott Jr (1877-1952) Geneseo; NY Senator, Letters to and from 1922-1932. Wadsworth, James Wolcott Jr. Prohibition and Repeal; 18th Amendment and Volstead Act. Box J112K Shelf 60
Wadsworth, James Wolcott Jr (1877-1952) Geneseo; NY Senator, Statement of opinion Wadsworth, James Wolcott, Jr. Prohibition enforcement Box J112J F 2 Sh 60
Wadsworth, James Wolcott Jr (1877-1952) Geneseo; NY Senator, Printed Materials, etc. Wadsworth, James Wolcott, Jr. Prohibition tracts; Texts of reports and speeches, etc. Box J112J Shelf 60
Wadsworth, James Wolcott Jr (1877-1952) Geneseo; NY Senator, Statement of opinion October 1930. Wadsworth, James Wolcott, Jr. Prohibition. Box J112J F 2 Shelf 60
Wadsworth, James Wolcott Jr (1877-1952) Geneseo; NY Senator, Speech 9/25/1930. Wadsworth, James Wolcott, Jr. Prohibition. See Also Statements of opinion. Box J112J F 2 Shelf 60
Wadsworth, James Wolcott Jr (1877-1952) Geneseo; NY Senator, Article, Herald Tribune 1935. Wadsworth, James Wolcott, Jr. Roosevelt, Franklin D., Criticism of. Box J112E F 27 Sh 59
Wadsworth, Jeremiah (1743-1804) Hartford financier, Letters to (71) 1793-1803. Wadsworth, James and William Family and Business. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Wadsworth, Jeremiah (1743-1804) Hartford financier, Map 1790's. Wadsworth, James (1768-f844) Genesee Valley holdings original manuscript, Map File #1 Main set
Wadsworth, Jeremiah (1743-1804) Hartford financier, Letter to April 26, 1793. Wadsworth, James (1768-1844) Genesee Valley lands; Reaction at first sight. Lib Congress Microfilm
Wadsworth, John (1781-1816) Correspondence, etc., 1800+. Wadsworth, John Wadsworth lands, etc. See Index Wads 3029.5 W125 A5. New York State Library
Wadsworth, John Noyes (1758-1814) Durham CT. Correspondence. etc., 1797-1814. Wadsworth, John Noyes (1758-1814) Wadsworth lands, etc. See Index Wads 3029.5 W125 A5. New York State Library
Wadsworth, John W Relative working in west with Joy Letters to (8) 1834-1845. Wadsworth, William Wolcott
Agent-(Book 58)
Farm business on Wadsworth lands in west. Box LBk 1 Sh 27-indexed
Wadsworth. Martha Blow (1864-1934) Avon equestrian;Wife, Photographs Circa 1904. Wadsworth, Herbert (1851-1927) Alaskan Boundary Survey trip. File cabinets
Wadsworth. Martha Blow (1864-1934) Avon equestrian;Wife, Photographs Circa 1900. Wadsworth, Herbert (1851-1927) Ashantee Estate in Avon. File cabinets
Wadsworth. Martha Blow (1864-1934) Avon equestrian;Wife, Photographs Circa 1900. Wadsworth, Herbert (1851-1927) Erie Canal. File cabinets
Wadsworth. Martha Blow (1864-1934) Avon equestrian;Wife, Photographs Circa 1900. Wadsworth, Herbert (1851-1927) Europe by automobile. File cabinets
Wadsworth. Martha Blow (1864-1934) Avon equestrian;Wife, Photographs Circa 1900. Wadsworth, Herbert (1851-1927) Great Lakes Steamboat Trip. File cabinets
Wadsworth. Martha Blow (1864-1934) Avon equestrian;Wife, Photographs Circa 1900. Wadsworth, Herbert (185f-1927) Horses: Hunt and rides from Washington to Avon. File cabinets
Wadsworth. Martha Blow (1864-1934) Avon equestrian;Wife, Photographs Circa 1900. Wadsworth, Herbert (1851-1927) Indian/Reservations in Southwestern United States. File cabinets
Wadsworth. Martha Blow (1864-1934) Avon equestrian;Wife, Photographs 1901. Wadsworth, Herbert (1851-1927) Pan-American Exposition in Buffalo NY. File cabinets
Wadsworth. Martha Blow (1864-1934) Avon equestrian;Wife, Photographs Before 1914. Wadsworth, Herbert (1851-1927) Panama Canal Construction. File cabinets
Wadsworth, Martha Blow, (1864-1934) Avon equestrian;Wife Lantern slides (118) Circa 1904. Wadsworth, Herbert (1851-1927) Alaskan Boundary Survey trip. Box 1 painted slides
Wadsworth, Martha Blow. (1864-1934) Avon equestrian;Wife Lantern slides (110) Circa 1900. Wadsworth, Herbert (1851-1927) Pack train trip from Fort Wingate to Rainbow Bridge. Box 2 painted slides
Wadsworth, Naomi Wolcott (1777-1831) Geneseo; Mother. Letters from (15) 1827-1830. Wadsworth, James S. and William W. Personal. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Wadsworth, Timothy L, Poem parody Wadsworth, Emmeline Austin Poem about Niagara Falls. Box LEAW2 F 25 Shelf 24
Wadsworth. Wedworth (1782-1860) Nephew from Durham CT Letter to September 25, 1816. Wadsworth, James (1768-1844) Church Bell for Geneseo; Advice on buying cattle. Bk 61 P 157 Shelf 27
Wadsworth, Wedworth (1782-1860) Nephew from Durham CT Letters to (10) September 21. 1815. Wadsworth, James (1768-1844) Morris Tract; Business matters. Bk 61 Sh 27 use index
Wadsworth, Wedworth (1782-1860) Durham CT. Correspondence, etc .. 1800+. Wadsworth, Wedworth (1782-1860) Wadsworth lands, etc. See Index Wads 3029.5 W125 A5. New York State Library
Wadsworth, Wedworth (1782-1860) Son, Durham CT, Letter from October 16, 1812. Wadsworth, John Noyes (1758-1814) War of 1812; capture of his Uncle William at Lewiston. Lib Congress Microfilm
Wadsworth, William Austin (1847-1918) "Major"; Geneseo Hunt Letters from (180) 1870-1885. Wadsworth, Emmeline Austin Family and Business. Box LEAW3 Shelf 24
Wadsworth, William Austin (1847-1918) "Major"; Geneseo Hunt Letters from (24) 1878-1879. Wadsworth, Herbert (1851-1927) Farm business and Investments. Box LHW1 Shelf 24
Wadsworth, William Wolcott (1810-1852) Geneseo farmer, Letters to (76) 1828-1831. Wadsworth, Elizabeth and family Family and Business. Index in print and on film Lib Congress Microfilm
Wadsworth, William Wolcott (1810-1852) Geneseo farmer, Documents (1 folder) 1845. Wadsworth, William Wolcott Manual Labor School for teaching Agricultural science. File Cab. I, Drawer 2
Wadsworth, William, General (1761-1833) Geneseo settler, Letters to (17) 1811-1821. Wadsworth, William (1761-1833)
Agent-Military Staff,
Military service during and after War of 1812. Box L 1 F 1 Shelf 15
Wadsworth, William, General (1761-1833) Geneseo settler, Documents (8 folders) 1810-1822. Wadsworth, William (1761-1833) Wadsworth Guards and Militia in the War of 1812. File Cab. I, Drawer 2